Guide to the Dr. Huey P. Newton Foundation Inc. Collection
Department of Special Collections
- Series 6; Audiovisual materials, 6
  - Subseries 1: Reel-to-Reel, 1
    - Connie Matthews, Mike Tabor, Kathleen Cleaver from 3/13/71 1758 On the Contradictions within the Black Panther Party. This is the second program on the subject to arrive from Algiers. Produced in New York on March 13, 1971 by Bruce Soloway. ...For Huey From Elsa 7.5ips reel 1 of 1 reel time ca. 55'1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Michael Tabor Reading the Document, Big Man -Bob Scheer Part 1a, Part 1 of 5, 3.75 i.p.s. full mono (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Huey Newton Discussing the Document 1b, Part 2 of 5, 3.75 i.p.s. full mono (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Huey Newton Discussing the Document and Answering Questions Part 1c, Part 3 of 5, 3.75 ips full mono (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Mass discussion with Huey Newton at the Constitutional Convention 1d, Part 4 of 5, 3.75 i.p.s. full mono (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Oakland Auditorium 3/5/71 Minister of Defense, Huey P. Newton, Revolutionary Intercommunal Day of Solidarity for Chairman Bobby Seale, Ruchell Magee - Ericka Huggins & Angela Davis & All Political Prisoners1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Liberalism-Report from RiveriaStates Hall, Mt. Vernon, New York 1e, Part 5 of 5 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      3.75 ips upper tr
    - Tape of Eldridge Cleaver recorded in Algiers on Jan. 12, 1971 - Leary - Drug Culture Etc. Transcript taken from tape. It is exact Elsa - KPFA recorded 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      7 1/2 i.p.s. [duplicated in cassette 11/20/94]
    - KDIA Radio Program "Black Montage" Sunday, April 30, 1972 Oakland, California 1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Jan 9 '73 Huey Newton - Tape #1 Studio B Intercommunalism 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      7 1/2 ips
    - Jan 9 '73 Huey Newton - Tape #2 Studio B H.P.N. Interview Historical-Dialectical Development1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Jan 9 '73 Huey Newton - Tape #3 Studio B Intercommunalism 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 5/22/73 Conversation SFPD Officers Cook & Koniaris w/ Ronald Louie Side 3 8-8a-8b1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Conversation 7/25/73 SFPD Cook & Koniaris w/ Ronald Louie 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      11/29/94: can't play - speed is 17/8 ips
    - Cal Massey (Box 3, Folder 6)
      monophonic 7.5 speed
    - "The Servant" Bishop Norman Williams (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Gwen- This is a copy of our 10 Pt. Platform and Program spoken by an actor hired by Addison-Wesley Publishing Company. They have already paid us to release it as part of a Teacher's Kit. Do you think it is o.k.? Michael [note included with tape] (Box 3, Folder 8)
      "Program and Platform/Black Panther Party 7 1/2 ips
    - Larry Diggs - KSFO Radio - Boycott & Ghetto You Black Business Ghetto Youth Movement KSFO (radio) 950 California San Francisco, Calif. 94108 (415)982-5500 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      duplicated to cassette 12/29/94
    - K. Cleaver's tapes 12/27/94 P.E. Type Lecture Re: Format BPP [on one reel unknown flute solo] (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - K. Cleaver's tapes 12/27/94 P.E. Type Lecture Re: Format BPP (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - K. Cleaver's tapes 12/27/94 P.E. Type Lecture Re Format BPP [on reel unknown speaker] (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Lumpen Reel 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      1. Power to the People, 2. Lumpen Theme, 3. People Get Ready (Freedom chant), 4. For Freedom (Pt. 1) 7.5 ips tape speed
    - Lumpen Reel 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      1. For Freedom (Part 2), 2. Bobby Must Be Set Free, 3. Ol' Pig Nixon, 4. Revolution in the Only Solution 7.5 ips tape speed
    - [on tape] OCS African Dance, Music Recital Direct: Toko Hall, Video: CAC (Box 4, Folder 7)
      includes note: "Huey This was done by video people from the Calif. Arts Council They edited it If you think it needs more, please let me know love,Ericka"
    - [unknown tape]1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      includes note from Richard Gibbs, 4/3/78 at Cowell College, Santa Cruz
    - #3 12/28/94 1 7/8 speed1994 (Othertype 5, Folder 1)
    - first 7 min of 4/30/72 KDIA-Statement Servant's Arrest1972 (Othertype 5, Folder 2)
    - [45 minute reel with no cover DeJur Grundig Brand--no label or date] (Othertype 5, Folder 3)
    - Lumpen/Panthers [1 of 2] (Othertype 18)
      Side one, one reel [as of 4/16/97 at conservation]
    - Lumpen/Panthers [2 of 2] (Othertype 19)
      Side two, one reel [as of 4/16/97 at conservation]
  - Subseries 2: Cassette, 2
    - [Interview with David Hilliard] (Othertype 5, Folder 4)
    - [Discussion of Algiers, other countries and other options. Possibly Eldridge Cleever] (Othertype 5, Folder 5)
    - [Answering machine tape] (Othertype 5, Folder 6)
    - [#5 Lecture and discussion on discrimination I] (Othertype 5, Folder 7)
    - [Music] (Othertype 5, Folder 8)
    - Gloria Estefan [music] (Othertype 5, Folder 9)
    - Lidell Townsell (Sides 1 and 2) -Nu Nu1992 (Othertype 6, Folder 1)
    - San Quentin Interview with Warden Louis Nelson 1668; [hw]continued property of Leon Huntting 1-3rd St. Sausalito, CA (Othertype 6, Folder 2)
    - Ron Dellums Prison Reform/BPP Boycott 257 (Othertype 6, Folder 3)
    - Funeral of Theodore "Bud" Hilliard Chairman Delivering Eulogy and Statement at Burial 7/5/73; Ted Bud Hilliard Memorial Service 17551973 (Othertype 6, Folder 4)
    - BPP Blues Ray Burns 01/01/77 16771977 (Othertype 6, Folder 5)
    - Son of Man Temple David DuBois Main Ad 11/18/73 1991973 (Othertype 6, Folder 6)
    - Minister of Information Message from Exile (E. Cleaver) 1754 (Othertype 6, Folder 7)
    - HPN Discussion w/ Bishop One Mine/Sex, Power, Women 1760 3); (Huey) Polic. General Discussion 4. (Othertype 6, Folder 8)
    - Huey Discusses Various Issues from CMC/David H Re 3/16/70 256; Copy David @ Federal Building re: Bobby, Huey 3/16/701970 (Othertype 6, Folder 9)
    - Newton Death Threat 03/06/78 16711978 (Othertype 6, Folder 10)
    - Huey P. Newton on Materialism 286; Discussion on Dialectical Materialism 8 (Othertype 6, Folder 11)
    - Bobby Seale Elaine Brown Press Conference Filing For Offices at City Hall 1/18/73 2211973 (Othertype 6, Folder 12)
    - Son of Man Temple David DuBois Main Ad 11/18/73 1991973 (Othertype 6, Folder 13)
    - Son of Man Temple Services Side 1&2 15 min #1 7/15/73 1981973 (Othertype 6, Folder 14)
    - Huey Speaks to BPP Members on Return From Cuba 08/03/77 1756 [hw:Return fr Cuba/E.B. Leadership]; Huey P. Newton at P.E. Class 3 August 1977 (dub) B1977 (Othertype 6, Folder 15)
    - Huey P. Newton Religion, Nationalism Love/Sex 248 (Othertype 6, Folder 16)
    - Huey to Charlie for Eldridge - Re Beverly Axelrod 7/9/70 16521970 (Othertype 6, Folder 17)
    - Huey P. Newton Assassination of Panther Member by US 8/19/69 2271969 (Othertype 6, Folder 18)
    - Definitions Terms Used in Lessons in Ownership-Encumbrances; Definitions Terms Used in Lessons in Math & Land-Contracts (Othertype 6, Folder 19)
    - Charles Perry 5/5/68 16221968 (Othertype 6, Folder 20)
    - Kathleen Cleaver Eldridge Cleaver Talk to David Mc 3/4/71 224 1971 (Othertype 6, Folder 21)
    - Mass Voter Registration Meeting St. Augustine's Church 2/2/73 2501973 (Othertype 6, Folder 22)
    - City Council Meeting 2/6/73 Chairman Proposes Anti-Secret Meeting Resolution 212 (recorded on both sides) 1972 - 1973 (Othertype 6, Folder 23)
    - C. Garry Interview w/ Witness - Daniels / Bradley on e 4/9/00; 4-9 Chuck Bradley1968 (Othertype 6, Folder 24)
    - Huey Newton From CMC East Two Statements 11/19/69 2841969 (Othertype 6, Folder 25)
    - Eldridge Cleaver on Prisons 294; Tape on Prisons by Eldridge (Othertype 6, Folder 26)
    - Huey P. Newton at New York Community College 11/19/76 269; Side 31976 (Othertype 6, Folder 27)
    - Cleaver on Shoot Out April 6 1968 4/25/68 16331968 (Othertype 6, Folder 28)
    - E. Brown Marian Bowdry Show/ Cleaver Belva Davis Show 8/6/76 2711976 (Othertype 6, Folder 29)
    - Tito to Huey 1631 (Othertype 6, Folder 30)
    - HPN on Reactionary Intercommunalism & El Toro 01/06/72 255; Fragile1972 (Othertype 6, Folder 31)
    - Cuba 1977 1/1/77 1681; HPN Cuba -771977 (Othertype 6, Folder 32)
    - Huey Newton to Johnny Spain from Cuba 218 (Othertype 6, Folder 33)
    - David Hilliard in Hayward CA #12 7/4/69 2821969 (Othertype 6, Folder 34)
    - Bobby Seale and Elaine Brown at Glide Memorial Church 01/28/73 28 min 11973 (Othertype 6, Folder 35)
    - Huey Newton Organizing with Bobby Seale in the Haight 228 (Othertype 6, Folder 36)
    - Palo Alto Bar Association Meeting 232 (Othertype 6, Folder 37)
    - Witness Shootout C. Gary 1/4/68 1635; Hoffman Bad Sound this side1968 (Othertype 6, Folder 38)
    - Huey Newton Interview with French Reporters on Part 9/20/72 219; Huey P. Newton on Ideology of BPP 9/20/721972 (Othertype 6, Folder 39)
    - Huey P. Newton on KGO TV Chan 7 Bay Scene w/ Claire 264 [hw 6/24 or 29/73; Sherman Skolnick's Report on Crash of "Watergate" Plane Carry Dorothy Hunt Aired on KPFA 263 Gene Jones Requested Copy Be Sent to You1973 (Othertype 6, Folder 40)
    - Stew Albert on Eldridge and Masai Marxist - 04/21/73 2801973 (Othertype 6, Folder 41)
    - David Hilliard - Face the Nation CBS 12/10/69 17511969 (Othertype 6, Folder 42)
    - Interview w/ Hratch [?] (Othertype 7, Folder 1)
    - [Unidentified] (Othertype 7, Folder 2)
    - Meeting re: Oakland, 1972 Sept. 21972 (Othertype 7, Folder 3)
    - Cal Massey (Othertype 7, Folder 4)
    - Garry TV-Channel 7 11/19/69 10:30am1969 (Othertype 7, Folder 5)
    - David Chicago Malcolm X College, 1969 Oct. 271969 (Othertype 7, Folder 6)
    - Channel 2 TV News Chairman Statement, 1972 Dec. 221972 (Othertype 7, Folder 7)
    - Wendell Wade -- Late May Music?; W. Wade on Org[an?]; Report on Elaine, 19721972 (Othertype 7, Folder 8)
    - Guderyon; Guderyon, Cheeves; Guderyon, Cheeves, Garcia, 1991 June 25-1991 June 281991 (Othertype 7, Folder 9)
    - 60 mins Dr. Mary Calderone, 1981 Dec. 25; Judith Arcana, Hour Magazine, 1983 Jun.; Letty Cotton Pogrebin, Charlie Rose Show, 1981 Feb. 2; Nancy Friday, Hour Magazine, 1981 Sept. 111981, 1983 (Othertype 7, Folder 10)
    - [Unidentified] (Othertype 7, Folder 11)
    - Babysitting; Elaine Brown Interview: Howard Levine and David Hilliard 1978-19901990 (Othertype 7, Folder 12)
    - 11/22/77 typed; side 2 - 11/22 - discussion1977 (Othertype 7, Folder 13)
    - Class 11/1/77 (typed); Class 2 Typed1977 (Othertype 7, Folder 14)
    - Reports on George Sams (Othertype 7, Folder 15)
    - Volume VIII 03504-03680; Volume VIII 03680-03843 (Othertype 7, Folder 16)
    - Vol. VIII 03844-04000 (Othertype 7, Folder 17)
    - Last Euben Lecture December (Othertype 7, Folder 18)
    - Statements by 1)Ed Schum 2)John Kamen (Othertype 7, Folder 19)
    - HPN - My Prison Rebellions 10/4 delicate tapes might break (Othertype 7, Folder 20)
    - Jan 5, 1985 Tony Norman1985 (Othertype 7, Folder 21)
    - Nixon's Announcement of Peace Treaty 1/23/73 14 min1973 (Othertype 7, Folder 22)
    - Lecture #5 Good Stories (Othertype 7, Folder 23)
    - Unknown Speaker (Othertype 7, Folder 24)
    - Alamena Lomax Bobby Seale--inaudible sound; Oleander Harrison, Huey, Ray Talifiero (Othertype 7, Folder 25)
    - Elaine Brown The Technology Question (Othertype 7, Folder 26)
    - Radio Mall 7/20/92 This Side!1972 (Othertype 7, Folder 27)
    - Huey -- Dec 29, 1969 Bad Sound1969 (Othertype 7, Folder 28)
    - Eldridge 3/1/711971 (Othertype 7, Folder 29)
    - Black Panthers in the South; Made[?] by Erskine Peters August 19791979 (Othertype 7, Folder 30)
    - BYEB: Editorial 10th Anniversary Issue, Oct. 16, 19761976 (Othertype 7, Folder 31)
    - New Haven 3-18-70 16511970 (Othertype 7, Folder 32)
    - Huey Newton Discussing the Document & Answering Questions Part 1C - 3 of 5 Bad Sound (Othertype 7, Folder 33)
    - Sun Jan 6 Girls-gun; Fri Jan 4 - Chg card statement (Othertype 7, Folder 34)
    - Contradiction Report; Report on Elaine, Starry[?] and Michael (Othertype 7, Folder 35)
    - For Huey Newton from George Jackson (Othertype 7, Folder 36)
    - Huey BPP Correct Example for Community 12/10/94 Bad? (Othertype 7, Folder 37)
    - For the Servant from Candi (Othertype 7, Folder 38)
    - Nov 17, 1977 done; discussion side1977 (Othertype 7, Folder 39)
    - Huey & ?; Huey & ? (Othertype 7, Folder 40)
    - Reel 1 Meeting Re: Oakland; Reel 1 August 2, 19721972 (Othertype 7, Folder 41)
    - Threats Blank; 1972 Gwyn F 4/18/70 S.P. Davis Shootout, Philadelphia June 1970 [scratched out]1972 (Othertype 7, Folder 42)
    - First Part of Other Side of Tape Dr. Small Re: Sickle Cell Program (Othertype 7, Folder 43)
    - Reel 2 Bert Schneider's Randolf (Othertype 7, Folder 43)
    - Bert Schneider's; Randolf Reel 1 (Othertype 7, Folder 44)
    - Son of Man Temple Chairman Delivering Sermon 9-23-731973 (Othertype 8, Folder 1)
    - Son of Man Temple Services October 14, 1973 Last Service at Old Church Chairman Delivering Message1973 (Othertype 8, Folder 2)
    - Son of Man Temple 8/26/731973 (Othertype 8, Folder 3)
    - Son of Man Temple Services (Last 3 minutes) Cassette 2 9/16/731973 (Othertype 8, Folder 4)
    - Dedication Ceremony (cont.) 10-21-73 cassette 2 of 41973 (Othertype 8, Folder 5)
    - Son of Man temple and intercommunal youth institute dedication ceremony cassette 1 of 4 10-21-731973 (Othertype 8, Folder 6)
    - Son of Man Temple Services 7-1-73 [Chairman Delivering Sermon]1973 (Othertype 8, Folder 7)
    - Son of Man Temple Services September 30, 1973 Comrade Bobby Delivering Sermon1973 (Othertype 8, Folder 8)
    - Message from Jimmy Carr to Huey. Please Erase & Return to Karen after he hears it or use it for message to send back to Jimmy (Othertype 8, Folder 9)
    - 1-5-77 Meeting with Jim Brewer; 1-5-77 Meeting wth Jim Brewer1977 (Othertype 8, Folder 10)
    - David Hilliard - 11-15-69 Vietnam Moritorium1969 (Othertype 8, Folder 11)
    - KLIF 570 am 3500 Maple at Turtle Creek, Dallas, TX 75219 (214) 526-2400 (Othertype 8, Folder 12)
    - Dr. Mary Calderone P.A.T. 1/21/83; Dr. Elinor Hamilton Hour Mag: Teaching Children About Sex 9/82, Dr. Mary Calderone People Are Talking 1/21/83 #16571982; 1983 (Othertype 8, Folder 13)
    - Chairman Speaks on 5/7/72 "Hidden Traitor" 12/10/94Bad?1972; 1994 (Othertype 8, Folder 14)
    - Report on Possible Parole Violation Baby Dee (Othertype 8, Folder 15)
    - Black Montage May 28, 72 Re: African Liberation Day Ron Bailey, Tanya Russel, Rickey Stevenson, Donald Williams; Black Montage 5/28/72 Re; African Liberation Day (5/27/72) 1.5 sides1972 (Othertype 8, Folder 16)
    - KDIA Black Montage 6/11/72 Tape II Side 1 Shirley Chisohlm; KDIA Black Montage 6/11/72 Tape II Side 2 Shirley Chisholm1972 (Othertype 8, Folder 17)
    - KDIA Black Montage June 11, 1972 Tape I; 2 Hrs 2 Tapes Servant, Angela Davis, Shirley Chisholm; KDIA Black Montage Tape I 6/11/72 Angela Davis & Family1972 (Othertype 8, Folder 18)
    - Copy Garry-Gain 9/13/731973 (Othertype 8, Folder 19)
    - Garry-Gain 9/13/731973 (Othertype 8, Folder 20)
    - 9-14-73 Chief Gaine and Charles Garry1973 (Othertype 8, Folder 21)
    - Charles Garry -April 6th Shootout Interviews Witness; Gwen1968 (Othertype 8, Folder 22)
    - E. Cleaver on Belva Davis Show 8/6/76 Part II 271 "B"1976 (Othertype 8, Folder 23)
    - Michael Tabor Reading the Document - Big Man - Bob Scheer Part 1-A - 1 of 5 (Othertype 8, Folder 24)
    - Stokely Carmichael at Howard 10-16-72 Part II1972 (Othertype 8, Folder 25)
    - Sunday January 8 #1 (Othertype 8, Folder 26)
    - Santa Clara County District Atty. Interview of Anthony Insana, 6-77 Tape I, Side 11977 (Othertype 8, Folder 27)
    - 10/27 Thurs typed 10/27/77; Save This side only - for Huey to listen to 10/27 class disc. class H. Missed1977 (Othertype 8, Folder 28)
    - 12-1-77; typed1977 (Othertype 8, Folder 29)
    - Nov 3 Thurs typed (Othertype 8, Folder 30)
    - #3 1/7/77 Meeting with Davie Harted [sp]1977 (Othertype 8, Folder 31)
    - #I 1/7/77 Meeting with Davie Harted[sp] 10am; #2 Davie Harted[sp]1977 (Othertype 8, Folder 32)
    - 11-15-77 typed; discussion1977 (Othertype 8, Folder 33)
    - To The Chairman & June From: Candi Re: Elaine (Othertype 8, Folder 34)
    - Tape 2 Lecture 3 1/25/791979 (Othertype 8, Folder 35)
    - Parkwoods - 5/22/76 @2211976 (Othertype 8, Folder 36)
    - CRG (? 1/95 seems blank) (Othertype 8, Folder 37)
    - Eldridge Cleaver Soul on Fire. 1976 Bible Voice, Inc., Box 7491, Van Nuys, California 914091976 (Othertype 8, Folder 38)
    - Harold Bell, Ronald "Doc" Satchel, Slim Coleman, Ericka and Mark A.; Chicago 5/13/78 1978 (Othertype 8, Folder 39)
    - Harold Bell, Ronald "Doc" Satchel, Slim Coleman, Ericka and Mark A.; Chicago 5/13/78 1978 (Othertype 8, Folder 40)
    - HPN The Technology Question; The Technology Question Huey P. Newton (Othertype 8, Folder 41)
    - Huey P. Newton Re: Marlon Scott Statement KDIA (Othertype 8, Folder 42)
    - First Part of Other Side of Tape Dr. Small Re: Sickle Cell Program (Othertype 8, Folder 43)
    - On Black Panther Party; Made by Erskine Peters August 19791979 (Othertype 8, Folder 44)
    - Huey P. Newton in Prison with Fay Stender #1747 12/15/94 Copy Before Rewinding Tape May Be Broken (Othertype 9, Folder 1)
    - Moziah; Report From Cuba (Moziah) (Othertype 9, Folder 2)
    - Moziah From Cuba 6/11/69 Continues on Second Tape1969 (Othertype 9, Folder 3)
    - Moziah from Cuba Tape #2 - 6/11/41; Discussion about unions - "Funds" Black guys "Turner"-"Okinawa" "Retirement Fund" Maritime Union (Othertype 9, Folder 4)
    - Copy of Tape Fm Willits Ans Machine Side 1 (30 min side onto 45 min tape;...side 2... (Othertype 9, Folder 5)
    - 2 of 2 Terra, Gatto, Redmond, Martinez 12:59 pm 3/12/82 Copy 2/14/841982 (Othertype 9, Folder 6)
    - Huey from Prison Copy of Fay Stender #1747 (Othertype 9, Folder 7)
    - Bonanno, Salvator 0610-137 12/6/78 McNeil1978 (Othertype 9, Folder 8)
    - Taylor-Bennett 10-31-741974 (Othertype 9, Folder 9)
    - #1B46 (A-1) Body Tape Copy 2/15/84 Nagra-Terra; Gatto; Bonanos, Sacramento 3/18/82 6:40pm (Othertype 9, Folder 10)
    - Side 1 Program ca32es 970002 3/7/79; side 2 program 1a32es 970002 3/7/79 [with card attached for Stephen C. Dodge Special Agent Department of the Treasury1979 (Othertype 9, Folder 11)
    - L. Terra & J. Bonano; S. Bonano; J. Gatto, V. Redmond, Mike Katz at Sacramento 3-17-82, 12:17pm (Othertype 9, Folder 12)
    - L. Terra & J. Bonano; S. Bonano; J. Gatto; V. Redmond; Mike Katz at Sacramento, 3/17/82, 12:17pm 1B43 _1982 (Othertype 9, Folder 13)
    - Sensory Deprivation (1) Donahue (6/29/81) Today Show (2) One Hour Magazine 12/28/81 (3) Evening Magazine (4) All the People (Nancy Graham Host); Sensory Deprivation (contd) All the People Nancy Graham (5) Sexual Dysfunction (6) Shere Hite1981 (Othertype 9, Folder 14)
    - 3. El Espanol Sin Esfuerzo (Othertype 9, Folder 15)
    - 2. El Espanol Sin Esfuerzo (Othertype 9, Folder 16)
    - Fathers in Divorce Side 3; Rod Bivings Seminars presents Fathers in Divorce Child Custody, Visitation, Support, Community Property Sponsored by United Fathers of America, Inc. Side 4 (Othertype 9, Folder 17)
    - S.F. Police (Othertype 9, Folder 18)
    - Witkin :Developments in California Substantive Law - 1969 A 3-hour Program by B.E. Witkin See Syllabus for Citations of Authorities. Topics Covered: Contracts; Real Property; Family Law, Community Property, and Wills; torts1969 (Othertype 9, Folder 19)
    - Witkin: Developments In California Substantive Law - 1969 A 3-hour Program by B.E. Witkin See Syllabus for Citations of Authorities. Topics Covered: Contracts; Real Property; Family Law, Community Property, and Wills; torts1969 (Othertype 9, Folder 20)
    - Practice Under the Family Law Act A Four Hour Course (Recorded Jan. 1970) FLA IV1970 (Othertype 9, Folder 21)
    - Practice Under the Family Law Act A Four Hour Course (Recorded Jan. 1970) FLA I1970 (Othertype 9, Folder 22)
    - Criminal Law Seminar...Hearsay: California and Federal Rules by Michael E. Tigar1978 (Othertype 9, Folder 23)
    - Civil Discovery -Tool or Weapon ...II1967 (Othertype 9, Folder 24)
    - CDI Civil Discovery 671967 (Othertype 9, Folder 25)
    - Criminal Law Seminar...Dealing with Prejudicial Publicity in Criminal Cases by William Kunstler1978 (Othertype 9, Folder 26)
    - Criminal Law Seminar: The Art of Objecting1978 (Othertype 9, Folder 27)
    - Environmental Law Conference Highlights 1970 UC Regents California Continuing Education of the Bar ENV/C I1970 (Othertype 9, Folder 28)
    - Environmental Law Conference Highlights ...1970 ENV/C II1970 (Othertype 9, Folder 29)
    - Environmental Law Conference ...Nov 6-8, 1970...ENV/C III1970 (Othertype 9, Folder 30)
    - Environmental Law Conference Highlights ENV/C III1970 (Othertype 9, Folder 31)
    - Environmental Law Conference Highlights ENV/C IV1970 (Othertype 9, Folder 32)
    - Definitions Terms Used in Lessons in Law-Finance; Definitions Terms Used in Lessons in Taxes-Appraisal (Othertype 9, Folder 33)
    - CACJ Criminal Law Seminar Language Goes to Court John Burgess San Francisco November 17, 19791979 (Othertype 9, Folder 34)
    - Fathers in Divorce Tape 4 (Othertype 9, Folder 35)
    - 7/15/74 Classification Civil Suit [including 6/31/74 note from "Cathy" to Garry re Johnny Spain's case]1974 (Othertype 9, Folder 36)
    - [Police report of arrest of Newton and Bay for the beating of a man in a bar. Very bad sound] (Othertype 9, Folder 37)
    - [Discussion between a man and a woman re: past expulsion of David Hilliard and other subjects. Very bad sound] (Othertype 9, Folder 38)
    - III 3/24/78? III (78/3/24)1978 (Othertype 10, Folder 1)
    - Tape II Hearing of Don Parks UC Med School O'ROurke Sept 28, 19701970 (Othertype 10, Folder 2)
    - Eagles; Doobie Brothers Greatest Hits [(Merry Christmas Karen)] (Othertype 10, Folder 3)
    - Under Cover Mix (Othertype 10, Folder 4)
    - Gerd Stern in Negril Raps Caribella Poems1981 - 1984 (Othertype 10, Folder 5)
    - Ulla Jones (Othertype 10, Folder 6)
    - Ulla Jones, Gambrinusgatan 6, 4tr., S-11231 STHLM, Sweden, tel. 08-53.52.50 "seems to be all music" 11/25/941994 (Othertype 10, Folder 7)
    - Slim's Album Master tape 12/29/93 (Othertype 10, Folder 8)
    - Slim's Album #2 (Othertype 10, Folder 9)
    - The Poetry of Thomas Hardy Read by Richard Burton (Othertype 10, Folder 10)
    - John Miller; More Wright (Othertype 10, Folder 11)
    - Elaine Brown - Seize the Time (Othertype 10, Folder 12)
    - Sensory Deprivation & Touching Nova Report (Othertype 10, Folder 13)
    - Forum: P.O.R. December 11, 1989 KQED-FM1989 (Othertype 10, Folder 14)
    - Barboura Morris Freed Oct. 22, 1932-Oct. 23, 1975 Memorial Services1975 (Othertype 10, Folder 15)
    - Barboura Morris Freed Oct. 22, 1932 - Oct. 23, 1975 Memorial Services1975 (Othertype 10, Folder 16)
    - Barboura Morris Freed Oct. 22, 1932 - Oct. 23, 1975 Memorial Services1975 (Othertype 10, Folder 17)
    - Report From Atlanta Georgia Alton Deville 10/16/721972 (Othertype 10, Folder 18)
    - Huey Newton Interview with Elsa Knight Thompson, KPFA 08/11/70 KPFA R/R Duplicated on Tape from Audio Tape R/R1970 (Othertype 10, Folder 19)
    - Chairman and Elaine at Glide Memorial Church 1-28-73 (She Sang the same selections both services) Side 1-Glide Mem Church 1/28/73 a)intro by ruth jones b)elaine singing and playing 2 selections c)chairman's 2nd speech d)chairman's 1st speech; Glide mem - cont. - chairman Speaking (1st speech)1973 (Othertype 10, Folder 20)
    - Stew Albert on Eldridge and ?; Skip w/ Al One1973 (Othertype 10, Folder 21)
    - #1752 11/21/69 Bobby Interview; 11/21/69 Bobby Interview cont.1969 (Othertype 10, Folder 22)
    - Candidates Night at Jefferson School 2-20-73 Cn&E; (1) Chairman and Elaine at Candidate's Night at Jefferson School 2-20-73 (cont.) (2) Ericka's Criticism of Comrades at P.E. Class 2-14-731973 (Othertype 10, Folder 23)